techcocktail.com 2019-07-20

# MVF Global Ltd

You have certain rights in relation to your data, including the right to object to processing based on legitimate interests, and direct marketing. At any time, you can exercise your rights by emailing us at [dataprotection@mvfglobal.com](mailto:dataprotection@mvfglobal.com). For further details about our processing and your rights, please see below.

## CONTENTS

* About our site
* About us
* What data we collect, and how we use it
* Requesting quotes
* Cookies
* Transferring your data
* Storing your data
* Legal grounds
* Your rights
* Contacting us
* Changes to this notice
* Cookies table

### About Our Site

Tech.co (" **our site** ") is an online resource for technology and related news and information.

### About Us

TechCo is a brand of Marketing VF Limited (" **MVF** ", " **we** ", " **us** ", " **our** ").

MVF is a company registered in England and Wales (company number: 06951544), whose registered office address is at Imperial Works, Perren Street, London NW5 3ED, United Kingdom.

For the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (the " **GDPR** "), Marketing VF Limited is the controller in relation to your data. We are registered as a controller with the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) under registration number Z1995728. You can confirm our registration here: www.ico.org.uk

### What Data We Collect, And How We Use It

**Subscribing to our newsletters:**

You can subscribe to our newsletters by completing and submitting the webform on our site. The webform will ask you for your first name, last name, email address, and newsletter preferences.

If you subscribe, we will send our newsletters to you periodically. At any time, you can unsubscribe by following the link in the newsletter.

**Contacting us:**

We will receive information about you if you contact us through our site, or by email or post. For example, to enquire about working with us, or with a news or press enquiry.

If you contact us, we will use your information to handle your enquiry and correspond with you.

**Working with suppliers:**

We work with a number of suppliers, who process data on our behalf. These include cloud storage providers, email service providers, and cloud telephony providers. We have appropriate contracts in place with such suppliers to ensure the protection and confidentiality of data.

**To run our competitions and prize draws:**

If you enter a competition or prize draw on our site, we will use the information that you provide to run the competition or prize draw, or contact you regarding your entry.

Where we are running a competition or prize draw jointly with another party, or promoting one of behalf of another party, we may share your entry details with that party, but only for the purposes of managing the competition or prize draw.

### Requesting Quotes

Some of the webforms on our site allow you to request quotes or information for different products and services (" **Quotes** ").

**What data we collect and how**

If you complete our webform in order to request Quotes, it will ask you for your contact details, such as your name, company name, email address, telephone number, and postal address. Our webform will also ask you for information regarding your product/service requirements.

From time to time, we change our webforms, and so they may ask you for other information. It will always be clear from the webform what information we’re requesting, and we only request information that is relevant to your request, and the service that we’re providing.

We also store and share Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, as explained below. Every computer or device has an IP address – a unique number – which enables it to communicate with other computers and devices over the Internet.

If we call you to confirm your details or requirements, we may ask you for some additional information.

We may monitor and/or record these calls for the purposes of quality control and staff training. Also, occasionally, we may need to provide Suppliers (as explained below) with limited access to such recordings in order to resolve queries and disputes.

**How we use your data**

**_To connect you with relevant Suppliers_**

As explained above, if you submit our webform, we’ll pass your request to one or more relevant product or service suppliers (named on the webform) ("Suppliers"). We will do this in a secure way. For example, using HTTP Secure (HTTPS), which means the data is encrypted. The Suppliers then contact you directly with your quotes. They may contact you by telephone, text/SMS or email.

Before we pass your request to any Suppliers, our service may involve an element of automated decision-making. Our technology platform may automatically assess your product/service requirements and pass your request to such Suppliers that would like to receive requests for Quotes at the time your request is made.

We store IP addresses in order to stop unwanted traffic (i.e. spam) to our site. For example, if we become aware that spam is coming from a particular IP address (i.e. computer or location), we can block that IP address. From time to time, we also share IP addresses with Suppliers to enable Suppliers to verify that requests for Quotes have come from a particular country.

**_To call you to confirm your details or requirements_**

For certain products/services, before connecting you with relevant Suppliers, we may call you to confirm your details or requirements.

We may also call you to ask about your experience using our site and service, and dealing with the Suppliers with which we connected you.

Withdrawing your consent - If, at any time, you wish to withdraw your consent to be contacted by us or the Suppliers regarding your request for Quotes, you can exercise this right by accessing our preference centre [https://preferences.safe-click.net](https://preferences.safe-click.net/).

**_To email you about similar products and services – But only if you haven’t opted out of such emails_**

If you use our quote request service, then, as an existing user, we would like to email you, or send you text/SMS messages, about similar products and services for which we think you might like quotes or information (" **Other Products** ").

You will always be given an opportunity to opt out of such messages before we send them, and we will not send such messages if you have opted out.

**_To create custom and lookalike/similar audiences_**

We like to work with Facebook, Google and other platforms (" **Platforms** ") to reach out to you with adverts for Other Products. We also like to use Platforms to reach out to other people who might like to use our quote request service.

We do this in two ways. In both cases, your data, along with other data, is used to create a custom audience and/or a lookalike/similar audience. Whenever an audience is shared with a Platform, the data is first hashed and pseudonymised, meaning that any data within the audience that could identify a person is replaced with an artificial identifier. So, the process is secure. Also, we don’t share more data than we need to for the purpose of creating the audience.

  * **Custom audience** – A custom audience is a list of existing users of our service (" **Existing Users** "). From time to time, we share this with Platforms. As explained above, the data is first hashed and pseudonymised. The Platform uses this audience to show our Existing Users our adverts for Other Products.
  * **Lookalike/similar audience** – A lookalike/similar audience is an audience created by the Platform. From time to time, we share with Platforms a list of Existing Users. The Platform uses this list to find and create lookalikes – i.e. other Platform users who have similar characteristics to the Existing Users – to which it shows our adverts. Again, as explained above, the data is first hashed and pseudonymised.

As we explain below, at any time, you may object to such activity by emailing us at [dataprotection@mvfglobal.com](mailto:dataprotection@mvfglobal.com).

**_Receiving data from Suppliers_**

From time to time, Suppliers may return data to us. They may do this if they have a query regarding a request for Quotes that we have sent to them in order to enable us to resolve the query. They may also return data to us, together with confirmation on whether or not a product has been purchased, in order to enable us to improve our marketing. We may also use such data to create custom and lookalike/similar audiences, as explained above.

### Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. At the bottom of this policy, we have included a table, setting out what cookies we use, and the purposes for which we use them.

Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org.

To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

### Transferring Your Data

We may transfer your data to countries outside the European Economic Area (the "EEA").

Some of those countries have a European Commission adequacy decision, which means they are considered to offer an adequate level of data protection.

Other countries do not have the same level of legal protection as countries in the EEA, or with an adequacy decision. If we do transfer your data in this way, we will take steps to ensure that it is protected to the same levels that apply in the EEA. This may include, for example, ensuring that the organisation receiving the data is registered with the EU-US Privacy Shield (in the case of transfers to the USA), or that we use the EU’s model contract clauses.

### Storing Your Data

We have a data retention policy, which clearly sets out how long we keep data for, and for what reasons.

We will keep your data only for as long as is necessary to fulfil the purpose/s for which it was collected in the first place, i.e. as set out in this notice.

### Legal Grounds

This notice sets out (above) how we use your data. Under the GDPR, controllers must have a valid lawful basis for each processing activity that they undertake. This section sets out our lawful basis for each activity.

**Activity** | **Lawful Basis under the GDPR**  
---|---  
Sending our newsletters to you | Consent  
Running competitions, prize draws, surveys, etc | Legitimate interests  
Handling enquiries received from you | Legitimate interests  
Connecting you with Suppliers | Consent  
Automated decision-making (as explained above) | Legitimate interests  
Using and sharing IP addresses | Legitimate interests  
Calling you to confirm your details or requirements | Consent  
Sharing call recordings with Suppliers | Legitimate interests  
Emailing you about Other Products | Legitimate interests  
Creating custom and lookalike/similar audiences | Legitimate interests  
Receiving data from Suppliers (as explained above) | Legitimate interests  
  
### Your Rights

Under the GDPR, you have a number of rights, which are explained below.

**Right of access** – You have the right at any time to ask us for a copy of the personal information that we hold about you, and to check that we are lawfully processing it.

**Right of rectification** – If personal information that we hold about you is not accurate or is out of date and requires amendment or correction you have a right to have the data rectified or completed.

**Right of erasure** – In certain circumstances, you have the right to request that personal information we hold about you is erased (e.g. if the information is no longer necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or processed).

**Right to object to or restrict processing** – In certain circumstances, you have the right to object to our processing of your personal information. For example, if we are processing your information on the basis of our legitimate interests, and there are no compelling legitimate grounds for our processing which override your rights and interests.

**Right of data portability** – In certain instances, you have a right to receive any personal information that we hold about you in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format.

**Right to withdraw consent** – In the limited circumstances where you may have provided your consent to the collection, processing and transfer of your personal information for a specific purpose, you have the right to withdraw your consent for that specific processing at any time.

**Exercising your rights**

If you wish to exercise any of your rights under the GDPR, please email us at [dataprotection@mvfglobal.com](mailto:dataprotection@mvfglobal.com). Alternatively, you can write to us at the address set out above, or inform us if you speak with us on the phone.

Our lead supervisory authority for the processing set out in this notice is the UK ICO. If you are unhappy with how we have processed your data, you have the right to make a complaint to the ICO.

If you are based outside of the UK, or you have a complaint concerning our activities outside of the UK, you may prefer to lodge a complaint with a different Supervisory Authority. A list of relevant authorities can be accessed here <http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080>.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions regarding this notice, or any questions relating to data protection or privacy, you can contact us at [dataprotection@mvfglobal.com](mailto:dataprotection@mvfglobal.com).

Alternatively, you can write to us at the address set out above.

### Changes To This Notice

From time to time, we may update this notice.

### Cookies Table

> **Cookie** | **Name** | **Purpose**  
---|---|---  
Universal Analytics (Google) | _ga  
_gali  
_gat_UA-1036645-1  
_gid  | These cookies collect information about how visitors use our website. We use the information to compile reports and to make improvements. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including where visitors have come to the website from and the pages they visited. To opt-out: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>  
Taboola Retargeting |  | These cookies are used to tailor Taboola adverts to a user’s previous viewing habits. For instance, if you have previously visited our page, you may then see other adverts related to that product or service. Taboola is an ad network that shows sponsored content, usually as links below the article on major news sites.  
Outbrain Retargeting |  | These cookies are used to tailor Outbrain adverts to a user’s previous viewing habits. For instance, if you have previously visited our page, you may then see other adverts related to that product or service. Outbrain is an ad network that shows sponsored content, usually as links below the article on major news sites.  
Adwords Retargeting (Google) |  | These cookies are used to adjust the targeting of our paid search and display advertising to show ads to users who have previously been to our sites and/or engaged with our page such as completing a form. They contain no personal information.  
DoubleClick Retargeting |  | These cookies are used to adjust the targeting of our display advertising to show ads to users who have previously been to our sites and/or engaged with our page such as completing a form. They contain no personal information.  
Hooly Media |  | These cookies are used to adjust the targeting of our display advertising to show video ads to users who have previously been to our sites. They contain no personal information.  
Taboola Conversion Tracking |  | These cookies measure ad conversions and optimise spend for advertising campaigns served on Taboola.  
Outbrain Conversion Tracking |  | These cookies measure ad conversions and optimise spend for advertising campaigns served on Outbrain.  
Adwords Conversion Tracking |  | These cookies measure when a user has completed an action on site such as completing a form. They contain no personal information.  
Bing Conversion Tracking | UET Tag | These cookies measure when a user has completed an action on site such as completing a form. They contain no personal information.  
DoubleClick Conversion Tracking |  | These cookies measure when a user has completed an action on site such as completing a form. They contain no personal information.  
Facebook Pixel |  | These cookies measure ad conversions, optimise and build audiences for advertising campaigns served on Facebook. To opt-out: <https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/>.   
Twitter Pixel |  | These cookies measure ad conversions and optimise advertising campaigns served on Twitter. To opt-out: <https://help.twitter.com/en/safety-and-security/privacy-controls-for-tailored-ads>  
LinkedIn Pixel |  | These cookies measure ad conversions, optimise and build audiences for advertising campaigns served on LinkedIn. To opt-out: <https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-policy>  
Pinterest Tag |  | These cookies are used to track conversions, optimise and build audiences to reach customers on Pinterest. To opt-out: <https://help.pinterest.com/en/articles/personalized-ads-pinterest>  
Skimlinks |  | Our website receives paid commission on sales of those products or services we write about. In some instances, we use a 3rd Party to enable these affiliate partnerships. To opt-out: <https://skimlinks.com/privacy-policy#users>  
Amazon Associates |  | These cookies track referral visits to Amazon for which we may earn commission for any eventual purchases.  
Adsense |  | AdSense uses cookies to improve advertising e.g. displaying targeted advertisements and avoiding showing advertisements that the user has already seen. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information.   
VWO | _vwo | These cookies are used to help us optimise our sites by running tests and measuring user conversions. It is also used to track user information when visiting the site (e.g. browser and device information).  
HotJar |  | Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behaviour (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click etc) and their devices (in particular device’s IP address, captured and stored only in anonymised form, preferred language settings etc). This enables us to better understand our users’ needs and to optimise this service and experience. Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymised user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. To opt out: <https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out>  
Tubemogul |  | This is used by our video player technology, Brightcove, to allow you to use the controls on our video player including play, pause, fast forward and rewind. Without this cookie you will not be able to watch our videos.   
Dianomioffers |  | This cookie tracks which of our reports and guides are of interest to our users.   
Infusionsoft |  | This cookie tracks when a user has completed a form on site. When the user revisits the site, this information will be pre-populated.   
  
**Last reviewed: 12 November 2018**
